alienvalley.com 2018-08-01

# AlienValley - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY - GENERAL INFO

At AlienValley.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by AlienvVlley.com and how it is used. 

This Privacy Policy regards the way in which AlienValley.com uses the information collected from its users. The Policy applies to all the content and the products and services offered by our website. 

## LOG FILES

Like many other Web sites, alienvalley.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

Alienvalley.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## USE OF INFORMATION

We collect user information to be used for the following purposes: 

\- To Process Payments. When you make a purchase we need the information you provide us such as name, email and credit card details so we can process your payment and deliver your purchased product to you.   
\- To improve customer service. The information you provide us helps us better understand our customers and therefore improve our support services more efficiently.   
\- Personalized user experience. We may use the collected information to improve the way users interact with our website and provide you with a better experience and help you find what you need faster.   
\- Product and Service improvement. Your feedback is important to us and we may use it to improve the quality of our products and services to better suit your needs.   
\- To send Emails. We send emails to the users who are interested in our freebies and the ones who want to join our newsletter to inform you about our newest products, services and deals. You can unsubscribe by informing us that you no longer wish to receive such messages by sending us an email using the contact form on our website. In addition, we may send you automated emails with download links when you request the download of a freebie. 

## ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

By using this website you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you don't agree to this policy you should stop using our website. Your continued use of AlienValley.com will be deemed your acceptance of the policy. 

## CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or wish more details regarding the way your personal information is used then please feel free to send ask us using the form available on our contact page.
